Guide to the Duke University Chapel Recordings, 1954-2002 UA.17.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Recordings, 1954-2002; 1
  - William Willimon - "No Partiality" Easter Service, 1986 March 30; 1458
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0321)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0001)
  - L. Bevel Jones - "The Future That Can Be", 1986 April 06; 1459
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0322)
  - James Cargas - Holocaust Memorial Service, 1986 April 10; 1460
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0323)
  - William Willimon - "Good Show", 1986 April 13; 1461
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0324)
  - Carol M. Cox - "What Manner of Person?", 1986 April 20; 1462
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0325)
  - William Willimon - "Is This All There Is?", 1986 April 27; 1463
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0326)
  - Peter J. Gomes - "Opportunity and Obstacles" Baccalaureate Service 8:30 am, 1986 May 04; 1464
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0327)
  - Peter J. Gomes - "Opportunity and Obstacles" Baccalaureate Service 10:30 am, 1986 May 04; 1465
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0328)
  - Peter J. Gomes - "Opportunity and Obstacles" Baccalaureate Service 3:00 pm, 1986 May 04; 1466
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0329)
  - Baccalaureate Service Organ Music, 1986 May 04; 1467
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0330)
  - William Willimon - "Freedom", 1986 May 11; 1468
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0331)
    - Copy - audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0332)
  - William Willimon - "Let's Get Together", 1986 May 18; 1469
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0333)
  - Carol M. Noren - "No Visible Means of Support", 1986 May 25; 1470
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0334)
  - William Willimon - "House of God", 1986 June 01; 1471
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0335)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Sanity and Christianity", 1986 June 08; 1472
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0336)
    - Copy - audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0337)
  - Lewis A. Briner - "Forgiven Much, We Can Have Love Much", 1986 June 15; 1473
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0338)
  - Nancy A. Ferree - "One in Christ", 1986 June 22; 1474
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0339)
  - Paula E. Gilbert - "Three Invitations - One Response", 1986 June 29; 1475
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0340)
  - William Willimon - "Prophets and the Powerful", 1986 July 06; 1476
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0341)
  - Jacob B. Golden - "The Naaman Syndrome", 1986 July 13; 1477
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0342)
  - Judi J. Smith - "Definitely Different", 1986 July 20; 1478
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0343)
  - William Willimon - "Teach Us to Pray", 1986 July 27; 1479
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0344)
  - Nancy A. Ferree - "On Possessing: The Way of Idolatry or Faith?", 1986 August 03; 1480
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0345)
  - H. Grady Hardin - "In the Mean Time", 1986 August 10; 1481
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0346)
  - Helen Neinast - "Plotters of the Resurrection", 1986 August 17; 1482
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0347)
  - William Willimon - "The Propriety of Praise", 1986 August 24; 1483
    - Audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0348)
    - Tape 1 - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 UMATIC-0002)
    - Tape 2 - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 UMATIC-0003)
  - William Willimon - "Mind Your Manners", 1986 August 31; 1484
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0349)
  - Chapel Congregation Anniversary Service 5:00 pm, 1986 September 07; 1485
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0350)
  - William Willimon - "The Cost of Discipleship", 1986 September 07; 1486
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0351)
  - James T. Laney - "Beyond the Bottom Line", 1986 September 14; 1487
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0352)
  - William Willimon - "On the Jericho Road", 1986 September 21; 1488
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0353)
  - Nancy A. Ferree - "In Search of the Ultimate…", 1986 September 28; 1489
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0354)
  - William Willimon - "Duty: Drudgery or Delight?", 1986 October 05; 1490
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0355)
  - Memorial Service for Wallace Wade, 1986 October 08; 1491
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0356)
  - Peggy Way - "Promises, Promises", 1986 October 12; 1492
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0357)
  - B. Maurice Ritchie - "The Parable of the Unjust Judge", 1986 October 19; 1493
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0358)
  - William Willimon - "Pharisees and Publicans All", 1986 October 26; 1494
    - Original audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0359)
  - William Willimon - "Victorious, Victims", 1986 November 02; 1495
    - Audiocassette (Box 33, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0360)
    - Tape 1 - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0004)
    - Tape 2 - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0005)
  - Thomas G. Long - "Jesus' Final Exam", 1986 November 09; 1496
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0361)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0006)
  - William Willimon - "Survival", 1986 November 16; 1497
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0362)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0007)
  - Sue Anne Steffey Morrow - "Refuge under God's Wings", 1986 November 23; 1498
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0363)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0008)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "On Not Knowing", 1986 November 30; 1499
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0364)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0009)
  - Handel's Messiah Part I, 1986 December; 1500
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0012)
  - Handel's Messiah Part II, 1986 December; 1501
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0013)
  - William Willimon - "Jews and Christians: All in the Family", 1986 December 07; 1502
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0365)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0010)
  - Dennis Campbell - "Forever Beginning" Founders' Day, 1986 December 14; 1503
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0366)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0011)
  - William Willimon - "God with Us", 1986 December 21; 1504
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0367)
  - William Willimon - "Light in the Darkness" Christmas Eve Service, 1986 December 24; 1505
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0368)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "The Journey Is Our Home", 1986 December 28; 1506
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0369)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0014)
  - John K. Bergland - "He Has Made Him Known", 1987 January 04; 1507
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0370)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0015)
  - William Willimon - "Who Am I?", 1987 January 11; 1508
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0371)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0016)
  - J. Barrie Shepherd - "Out of the Depths", 1987 January 18; 1509
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0372)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0017)
  - William Willimon - "Seeing Is Believing", 1987 January 25; 1510
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0373)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0018)
  - Anne E. Hockridge - "Concrete Mysteries", 1987 February 01; 1511
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0374)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 40, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0019)
  - William Willimon - "On Rendering to God and to Caesar", 1987 February 08; 1512
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0375)
    - Copy - audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0376)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0020)
  - Clyde Fant - "The Yoke No One Can Bear", 1987 February 15; 1513
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0377)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0021)
  - William Willimon - "A Second Look", 1987 February 22; 1514
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0378)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0022)
  - Helen G. Crotwell - "The Holy Mountain", 1987 March 01; 1515
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0379)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0023)
  - H. Grady Hardin - "God under Pressure", 1987 March 08; 1516
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0380)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0024)
  - Roy C. Nichols - "Redeeming the Future", 1987 March 15; 1517
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0381)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0025)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "Encounter at the Well", 1987 March 22; 1518
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0382)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0026)
  - William Willimon - "Proclaiming Death", 1987 March 29; 1519
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0383)
  - Elizabeth Achtemeier - "The Safari and the Lion", 1987 April 05; 1520
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0384)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0027)
  - William Willimon - "Downward Mobility" Palm Sunday Service, 1987 April 12; 1521
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0385)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0028)
  - William Willimon and Nancy A. Ferree - "Company of Betrayers" Good Friday Service, 1987 April 17; 1522
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0386)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0387)
  - William Willimon - "The Last Laugh", 1987 April 19; 1523
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0388)
    - Copy - audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0389)
  - Richard Lischer - "Doubt", 1987 April 26; 1524
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0390)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0029)
  - William Willimon - "Easter Is True", 1987 May 03; 1525
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0391)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0030)
  - David H. C. Read - "Knowledge - With Room for Wonder" Baccalaureate Service 5:00 pm, 1987 May 08; 1527
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0392)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0031)
  - David H. C. Read - "Knowledge - With Room for Wonder" Baccalaureate Service 3:00 pm, 1987 May 09; 1528
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0393)
  - David H. C. Read - "Knowledge - With Room for Wonder" Baccalaureate Service 11:00 am, 1987 May 09; 1529
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0394)
  - Margaret B. Via - "Endings and Beginnings", 1987 May 10; 1530
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0395)
  - Ted Koppel - Commencement Address, 1987 May 10; 1531
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0396)
  - William Willimon - "When Bad Things Happen to Good People", 1987 May 17; 1532
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0397)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0032)
  - Michael Williams - "The Unknown People and the Unknown God", 1987 May 24; 1533
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0398)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0033)
  - Rosemary Radford Reuther - "Encountering Christ in the Form of Our Sister", 1987 May 31; 1534
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0399)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0034)
  - John Hewett - "The Spirit and the Forms of Freedom", 1987 June 07; 1535
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0400)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0035)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "In the Beginning", 1987 June 14; 1536
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0401)
  - Ted Campbell - "On Confessing Faith in Christ", 1987 June 21; 1537
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0402)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0036)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "Face to Face", 1987 June 28; 1538
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0403)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0037)
  - William H. Willimon - "Sin", 1987 July 05; 1539
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0404)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0038)
  - Paula E. Gilbert - Sermon Untitled, 1987 July 12; 1540
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0405)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 41, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0039)
  - Carol M. Noren - "When Visions Aren't Enough", 1987 July 19; 1541
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0406)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0040)
  - William H. Willimon - "God's Little Acre", 1987 July 26; 1542
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0407)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0041)
  - Leonard I. Sweet - "Pigeon-Walking, Whale-Watching, Wave-Riding, Water-Striding", 1987 August 02; 1543
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0408)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0042)
  - Louis Patrick - "Getting It Together", 1987 August 09; 1544
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0409)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0043)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "The Essence of Murmuring", 1987 August 16; 1545
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0410)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0044)
  - William H. Willimon - "Letting God Be God", 1987 August 23; 1546
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0411)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0045)
  - William H. Willimon - "Clean Hands", 1987 August 30; 1547
    - Audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0412)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0046)
  - William H. Willimon - "Advice", 1987 September 06; 1548
    - Audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1114)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0047)
  - William H. Willimon - "Choice, Chance, or the Hand of God?", 1987 September 13; 1549
    - Audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1115)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0048)
  - William H. Willimon - "Choices", 1987 September 20; 1550
    - Audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1116)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0049)
  - William H. Willimon - "Remember Not…Remember Me", 1987 September 27; 1551
    - Audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1117)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0050)
  - Heather Murray Elkins - "The Song of Stones", 1987 October 04; 1552
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0051)
  - William H. Willimon - "Thanks, but…", 1987 October 11; 1553
    - Audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1118)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0052)
  - John W. Vannorsdall - "On Hailing Caesar", 1987 October 18; 1554
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0053)
  - Peter J. Storey - Sermon Untitled, 1987 October 25; 1555
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0054)
  - William Willimon - "Blessed Are the Poor in Spirit", 1987 November 01; 1556
    - Audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1119)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0055)
  - Richard Lischer - "Let It Rain", 1987 November 08; 1557
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0056)
  - Anthony Campolo - "The Incognito God", 1987 November 15; 1558
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0057)
  - Carol M. Noren - "A Matter of Motives", 1987 November 22; 1559
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0058)
  - Eugene Lowery - "Who Could Ask for Anything More?", 1987 November 29; 1560
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 42, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0059)
  - William Willimon - "The Way of (to) Peace", 1987 December 06; 1561
    - Audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1120)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0060)
  - Handel's Messiah - conducted by J. Benjamin Smith, 1987 December 06; 1562
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0061)
  - Thomas B. Stockton - "Eating from Vineyards We Did Not Plant" Founders' Day, 1987 December 13; 1563
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0062)
  - William Willimon - "Who His People Were", 1987 December 20; 1564
    - Audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1121)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0063)
  - William Willimon - "The Great Resumption after the Grand Intrusion", 1987 December 27; 1565
    - Audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1122)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0064)
  - Grant F. Shockley - "The Star in the East", 1988 January 03; 1566
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0065)
  - Peter Gomes - "Religion of the Dawn", 1988 January 10; 1567
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0066)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "Desire", 1988 January 17; 1568
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0067)
  - William Willimon - "Immediately, They Followed", 1988 January 24; 1569
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0068)
  - Beverly Gaventa - "Openly and Unhindered", 1988 January 31; 1570
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0069)
  - David C. Steinmetz - "For the Sake of the Gospel", 1988 February 07; 1571
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0070)
  - William Willimon - "Love in Action", 1988 February 14; 1572
    - Audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1123)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0071)
  - William Willimon - "That God Will Be God", 1988 February 21; 1573
    - Audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1124)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0072)
  - Steven Shoemaker - "The Foolishness of God", 1988 March 06; 1574
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0073)
  - James A. Sanders - "Annunciations", 1988 March 13; 1575
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0074)
  - Shelly Wilson Wall - "Unremarkability", 1988 March 20; 1576
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0075)
  - William Willimon - "A Violent Week", 1988 March 27; 1577
    - Audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1125)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0076)
  - William Willimon - "Failure" Easter Service, 1988 April 03; 1578
    - Original audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1126)
  - Walter Wangerin, Jr. - "The Witnesses of These Things", 1988 April 17; 1579
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0077)
  - Elizabeth Achtemeier - "Audacious Claim", 1988 April 24; 1580
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0078)
  - David E. Jenkins - "Power and Powerlessness", 1988 May 01; 1581
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 43, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0079)
  - Margaret B. Via - "What in the World Is God Doing?", 1988 May 08; 1582
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 44, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0080)
  - William C. Turner - "Living at Its Best", 1988 May 15; 1583
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 44, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0081)
  - William Holmes - "Mystery, 'Mistakes', and Bois d'Arc Trees", 1988 May 22; 1584
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 44, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0082)
  - Joan Salmon - Campbell - "Come on, Let's Party", 1988 June 06; 1585
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 44, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0083)
  - John Wall - Untitled, 1988 June 12; 1586
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 44, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0084)
  - Joanna Adams - "Wait to the Children", 1988 June 28; 1587
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 44, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0085)
  - Robert Capon - "No Mighty Work", 1988 July 02; 1588
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 44, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0086)
  - Chester Williams - "That Special Race", 1988 July 10; 1589